Fletcher School Records UA015
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
- Special programs and projects, 1949 -- 1988; 1965 -- 1987; UA015.010; 12.0 Linear Feet
  - Minutes of meetings, project Niger, 1983 -- 1984; UA015.010.060.00028 (Box 60)
  - Minutes of meetings, project Niger, 1984; UA015.010.060.00029 (Box 60)
  - Minutes, Senior Advisory Group (SAG), 1984 -- 1987; UA015.010.060.00030 (Box 60)
  - Mobilization expenditures, 1982 -- 1984; UA015.010.060.00031 (Box 60)
  - News releases, Tufts in-house, 1983; UA015.010.060.00032 (Box 60)
  - Newsletter information, NILP, 1984; UA015.010.060.00033 (Box 60)
  - Newsletter, photographs, UA015.010.060.00034 (Box 60)
  - NILP, Plan de Travail, 1987; UA015.010.060.00035 (Box 60)
  - NILP, planning, 1982 -- 1983; UA015.010.060.00036 (Box 60)
  - NILP, talloires, 1984; UA015.010.060.00037 (Box 60)
  - NILP, evaluation, 1985 -- 1987; UA015.010.060.00038 (Box 60)
  - NILP, evaluation: Briefing Paper, 1985; UA015.010.060.00039 (Box 60)
  - NILP, evaluation: Tufts internal, 1985 -- 1988; UA015.010.060.00040 (Box 60)
  - NILP, evaluation response, 1985 -- 1986; UA015.010.060.00041 (Box 60)
  - NILP, Plan d' Action, 1984 -- 1985; UA015.010.060.00042 (Box 60)
  - NILP, project analysis, 1983; UA015.010.060.00043 (Box 60)
  - NILP, project data sheet, UA015.010.061.00001 (Box 61)
  - NILP, project grant agreement, UA015.010.061.00002 (Box 61)
  - NILP, project grant agreement information, 1983; UA015.010.061.00003 (Box 61)
  - NILP Project Paper, 1983; UA015.010.061.00004 (Box 61)
  - NILP Project Paper, Annex A, 1983; UA015.010.061.00005 (Box 61)
  - NILP Project Paper, Annex B, C, 1983; UA015.010.061.00006 (Box 61)
  - NILP Project Paper, Annex 6, UA015.010.061.00007 (Box 61)
  - NILP Project Paper, Annex 8, UA015.010.061.00008 (Box 61)
  - NILP Project Paper, Annex 9, UA015.010.061.00009 (Box 61)
  - NILP Project Paper, Annex 10, UA015.010.061.00010 (Box 61)
  - NILP Project Paper, Annex 12, UA015.010.061.00011 (Box 61)
  - NILP Project Paper, Annex 13, UA015.010.061.00012 (Box 61)
  - NILP Project Paper, Annex 14, UA015.010.061.00013 (Box 61)
  - NILP Project Paper, Annex 15, UA015.010.061.00014 (Box 61)
  - NILP Project Paper, Annex 16, 1983; UA015.010.061.00015 (Box 61)
  - NILP Project Paper, Annex 20, UA015.010.061.00016 (Box 61)
  - NILP Project Paper, tables, UA015.010.061.00017 (Box 61)
  - NILP Statement of work, UA015.010.061.00018 (Box 61)
  - NILP Terms and conditions of services, 1983; UA015.010.061.00019 (Box 61)
  - NILP, training, 1985 -- 1986; UA015.010.061.00020 (Box 61)
  - Niger Range and Livestock Project, Animal Disease Patter Paper: Part 1, 1981; UA015.010.061.00021 (Box 61)
  - Niger Range and Livestock Project, Animal Disease Patter Paper: Part 2, 1981; UA015.010.061.00022 (Box 61)
  - Niger Range and Livestock Project, Briefing papers, UA015.010.061.00023 (Box 61)
  - Niger Range and Livestock Project, Briefing papers, continued, UA015.010.061.00024 (Box 61)
  - Niger Range and Livestock Project, Project description, UA015.010.061.00025 (Box 61)
  - Oversight Committee, 1985; UA015.010.061.00026 (Box 61)
  - Position Paper, UA015.010.061.00027 (Box 61)
  - Procurement, 1983 -- 1987; UA015.010.061.00028 (Box 61)
  - Procurement plan, 1983 -- 1986; UA015.010.061.00029 (Box 61)
  - Procurement telex, 1984 -- 1985; UA015.010.061.00030 (Box 61)
  - Professional profile, 1983; UA015.010.061.00031 (Box 61)
  - Project Elevage Integre Resume Historique et Propositions, 1988; UA015.010.061.00032 (Box 61)
  - Publication lists/ bibliography, 83, 1980 -- 1983; UA015.010.061.00033 (Box 61)
  - Publications related to Africa and pastoralism, 1984 -- 1986; UA015.010.061.00034 (Box 61)
  - Publicity reports, UA015.010.061.00035 (Box 61)
  - Quarterly cost summaries, 1984 -- 1988; UA015.010.061.00036 (Box 61)
  - Reports, Cook, 1984 -- 1987; UA015.010.061.00037 (Box 61)
  - Reports, Loutan 1985-86, 1985 -- 1986; UA015.010.061.00038 (Box 61)
  - Reports, Metzel, 86, 1984 -- 1986; UA015.010.061.00039 (Box 61)
  - Reports, Michel, 1985; UA015.010.061.00040 (Box 61)
  - Reports, Pase, 1984 -- 1986; UA015.010.061.00041 (Box 61)
  - Reports, Shaw, 1984; UA015.010.061.00042 (Box 61)
  - Reports, weekly summary, 1985 -- 1986; UA015.010.061.00043 (Box 61)
  - Rural Health Improvement Project, 1983; UA015.010.061.00044 (Box 61)
  - Steel and ore economy, 1975 -- 1976; UA015.010.061.00045 (Box 61)
  - Strategy Paper, UA015.010.062.00001 (Box 62)
  - Telex: Incomming, 1983 -- 1984; UA015.010.062.00002 (Box 62)
  - Telex: Incomming, 1986; UA015.010.062.00003 (Box 62)
  - Telex: Incomming, 1986; UA015.010.062.00004 (Box 62)
  - Telex: Incomming, 1986; UA015.010.062.00005 (Box 62)
  - Telex: Incomming, 1986; UA015.010.062.00006 (Box 62)
  - Telex: Incomming, 1986; UA015.010.062.00007 (Box 62)
  - Telex: Incomming, 1987; UA015.010.062.00008 (Box 62)
  - Telex, Incomming, 1987; UA015.010.062.00009 (Box 62)
  - Telex: Incomming, 1988; UA015.010.062.00010 (Box 62)
  - Telex: Incomming, 1988; UA015.010.062.00011 (Box 62)
  - Telex: Incomming, 1988; UA015.010.062.00012 (Box 62)
  - Telex: Incomming, 1988; UA015.010.062.00013 (Box 62)
  - Telex: Incomming, various, 1988; UA015.010.062.00014 (Box 62)
  - Telex log, 1984; UA015.010.062.00015 (Box 62)
  - Telex: Outgoing, 1982 -- 1983; UA015.010.062.00016 (Box 62)
  - Telex: Outgoing, 1983; UA015.010.062.00017 (Box 62)
  - Telex: Outgoing, 1984; UA015.010.062.00018 (Box 62)
  - Telex: Outgoing, 1986; UA015.010.062.00019 (Box 62)
  - Telex: Outgoing, 1986; UA015.010.062.00020 (Box 62)
  - Telex: Outgoing, 1986; UA015.010.062.00021 (Box 62)
  - Telex: Outgoing, 1986; UA015.010.062.00022 (Box 62)
  - Telex: Outgoing, 1986; UA015.010.062.00023 (Box 62)
  - Telex: Outgoing, 1986; UA015.010.062.00024 (Box 62)
  - Telex: Outgoing, 1986; UA015.010.062.00025 (Box 62)
  - Telex: Outgoing, 1986 -- 1987; UA015.010.062.00026 (Box 62)
  - Telex: Outgoing, 1987; UA015.010.062.00027 (Box 62)
  - Telex: Outgoing, 1987; UA015.010.062.00028 (Box 62)
  - Telex: Outgoing, 1988; UA015.010.062.00029 (Box 62)
  - Telex: Outgoing, 1988; UA015.010.062.00030 (Box 62)
  - Telex: Outgoing, 1988; UA015.010.062.00031 (Box 62)
  - Telex: Outgoing, 1988; UA015.010.062.00032 (Box 62)
  - Telex: Outgoing, Aug- Oct 1988, UA015.010.062.00033 (Box 62)
  - Terms to translate, UA015.010.062.00034 (Box 62)
  - Title XII, 1981 -- 1984; UA015.010.062.00035 (Box 62)
  - Trading and export companies, 1984; UA015.010.062.00036 (Box 62)
  - Travel reports, 1984; UA015.010.062.00037 (Box 62)
  - Travel schedules, 1982 -- 1983; UA015.010.062.00038 (Box 62)
  - United Nations Childrens Fund (UNICEF): Introduction packet on Niger, 1984; UA015.010.062.00039 (Box 62)
  - Water Survey, Niger Range and Livestock Project, 1981; UA015.010.062.00040 (Box 62)
  - Payment in Prospect (with photocopies of Holt farm and persons), UA015.010.063.00001 (Box 63)
  - Petroleum companies, 1975; UA015.010.063.00002 (Box 63)
  - Plan: Clayton Center, UA015.010.063.00003 (Box 63)
  - Projects: Cuba and Paraguay, 1975; UA015.010.063.00004 (Box 63)
  - Recent developments in E-W trade (magazine clippings), 1975; UA015.010.063.00005 (Box 63)
  - Research to Maximise, John B. Holt essays, 1974 -- 1976; UA015.010.063.00006 (Box 63)
  - Resolution: ACSA Convention, CTJ clipping, 1952; UA015.010.063.00007 (Box 63)
  - Romania: Economic development publications, 1971 -- 1980; UA015.010.063.00008 (Box 63)
  - Southern Educational and Charitable Trust, correspondance, 1953 -- 1955; UA015.010.063.00009 (Box 63)
  - Romania: publications, 1971 -- 1974; UA015.010.063.00010 (Box 63)
  - Romania: publications on business venture, 1973 -- 1977; UA015.010.063.00011 (Box 63)
  - So- White Soap Company case, UA015.010.063.00012 (Box 63)
  - Strategies by industry, drafts, UA015.010.063.00013 (Box 63)
  - Strategies summary, 1976; UA015.010.063.00014 (Box 63)
  - Section II: extended company reports, 1976; UA015.010.063.00015 (Box 63)
  - Section II: Summary of findings and recommendations, UA015.010.063.00016 (Box 63)
  - Subject matter for interviews, UA015.010.063.00017 (Box 63)
  - Table: Degree of involvement, UA015.010.063.00018 (Box 63)
  - Taylor, Mr. A. Starke, correspondance, 1949 -- 1953; UA015.010.063.00019 (Box 63)
  - Telecommunication equipment cost, 1975 -- 1977; UA015.010.063.00020 (Box 63)
  - UNITAR and DTBA reports, 76, 1971 -- 1976; UA015.010.063.00021 (Box 63)
  - U.S. Congress, correspondance, 1976 -- 1977; UA015.010.063.00022 (Box 63)
  - U.S. Congress, correspondance: Collins- Griffin, 1970 -- 1975; UA015.010.063.00023 (Box 63)
  - U.S. Congress, correspondance: Gurney- MacDonald, 1971 -- 1977; UA015.010.063.00024 (Box 63)
  - U.S. Congress, correspondance, Magnuson- Springer, 1971 -- 1977; UA015.010.063.00025 (Box 63)
  - U.S. Congress, correspondance, Stevenson- Talmadge, 1970 -- 1975; UA015.010.063.00026 (Box 63)
  - U.S. Fundraising reports, 1974; UA015.010.063.00027 (Box 63)
  - The United States Oil Field Service and Supply Industry, Introduction, 1978; UA015.010.063.00028 (Box 63)
  - The United States Oil Field Service and Supply Industry, Sections I-III, 1978; UA015.010.063.00029 (Box 63)
  - The United States Oil Field Service and Supply Industry, Section IV, 1978; UA015.010.063.00030 (Box 63)
  - U.S. Pharmaceuticals in E.E. [Eastern Europe?], Knickerbocker and Brada comments on draft, 1977; UA015.010.063.00031 (Box 63)
  - Universidad de Carabobo, Venezuela, 1977; UA015.010.063.00032 (Box 63)
  - Universidad Centro Occidental, 1977; UA015.010.063.00033 (Box 63)
  - Universidad de Costa Rica, 1976 -- 1977; UA015.010.063.00034 (Box 63)
  - Universidad de los Andes, Faculty of Arts and Sciences, 1977; UA015.010.063.00035 (Box 63)
  - Universidad Metropolitano, Venezuela, 1977; UA015.010.063.00036 (Box 63)
  - Universidad de Oriente, Venezuela, 1977; UA015.010.063.00037 (Box 63)
  - Universidad Nacional de Tachira, Venezuela, 1977; UA015.010.063.00038 (Box 63)
  - Universidad de Valle, Guatemala, 1977 -- 1978; UA015.010.063.00039 (Box 63)
  - USSR- U.S. business relations: essays and publications, 1971 -- 1977; UA015.010.063.00040 (Box 63)
  - Venezuelan- American Conference, Correspondance, 1974 -- 1975; UA015.010.064.00001 (Box 64)
  - Venezuelan- American Conference, Invitations, acceptances, regrets, 1974 -- 1975; UA015.010.064.00002 (Box 64)
  - Venezuelan- American Conference, Preparations including telex, 1974 -- 1975; UA015.010.064.00003 (Box 64)
  - Venezuelan- American Conference, various documents, 1974 -- 1975; UA015.010.064.00004 (Box 64)
  - Venezuelan ledership and U.S. relations, including conferences, 1974 -- 1975; UA015.010.064.00005 (Box 64)
  - Venezuelan oil industry information, 1976 -- 1977; UA015.010.064.00006 (Box 64)
  - Venezuelan relations: various reports and correspondance, 1974 -- 1975; UA015.010.064.00007 (Box 64)
  - Venezuelan Symposium, Spring, 1975; UA015.010.064.00008 (Box 64)
  - Venezuelan Symposium, various documents and correspondance, 1974 -- 1976; UA015.010.064.00009 (Box 64)
  - Venezuela- Telex and Western Union communications, 1974 -- 1975; UA015.010.064.00010 (Box 64)
  - Venezuelan- U.S. Symposium, Parts I- IV, 1975; UA015.010.064.00011 (Box 64)
  - West German and U.S. experience with joint ventures in Yugoslavia, 1972; UA015.010.064.00012 (Box 64)
  - West German experience with joint ventures in Yugoslavia, a study, 1972; UA015.010.064.00013 (Box 64)
  - Yugolsavia, background, 1971; UA015.010.064.00014 (Box 64)
  - Yugoslavia joint ventures, including government publications, 1969 -- 1973; UA015.010.064.00015 (Box 64)
- Reports, publications, and newsletters, 1957 -- 2018; UA015.011; 2.45 Linear Feet; 7 Digital Object(s); 134.1 Megabytes
  This series contains published materials emanating from the Fletcher school. Some booklets or pamphlets describe various Fletcher programs, the student body, and faculty. Other materials included in this series are those published by faculty or students, speakers who have given an address at the Fletcher School, or news clips which mention the Fletcher School, its faculty or its research. This series also includes electronic files housed on the Internet Archive.
  - The Atlantic Grows Wider. Address by H.E. Sir Oliver Wright, 1983; UA015.011.065.00001 (Box 65)
  - The Cape Route: Imperiled Western Lifeline. Special Report, 1981; UA015.011.065.00002 (Box 65)
  - Career Planning/ Development Guide-88, 1984 -- 1988; UA015.011.065.00003 (Box 65)
  - China: Prospects for the Future of the "Middle Kingdom." Commencement address by Winston Lord, UA015.011.065.00004 (Box 65)
  - Contrasting Modernization in China and Japan. By Allan B. Cole, 1966; UA015.011.065.00005 (Box 65)
  - Corporate Affiliate Program, informational booklet, 1980; UA015.011.065.00006 (Box 65)
  - Employers Guide to the Fletcher School, 1984 -- 1986; UA015.011.065.00007 (Box 65)
  - Employers Guide to the Fletcher School, 1990 -- 1993; UA015.011.065.00008 (Box 65)
  - Energy Issues and Alliance Relationships: The United States, Western Europe and Japan. Special Report, 1980; UA015.011.065.00009 (Box 65)
  - Faculty, 1970; UA015.011.065.00010 (Box 65)
  - Fletcher Associates. Information pamphlet, UA015.011.065.00011 (Box 65)
  - Force Reductions in Europe: Starting Over. Special Report, 1980; UA015.011.065.00012 (Box 65)
  - Graduates in the United States Foreign Service, 1970; UA015.011.065.00013 (Box 65)
  - Guide to International Affairs Experts, 1988 -- 1994; UA015.011.065.00014 (Box 65)
    Contains the media guides for 1988, 1990-91, and 1993-94.
  - Humphrey- Fletcher Visiting Fellows Program. Informational pamphlet, 1989 -- 1990; UA015.011.065.00015 (Box 65)
  - International Security Dimensions of Space. Conference Report, 1982; UA015.011.065.00016 (Box 65)
  - International Security Studies Program. Informational booklet, 1994; UA015.011.065.00017 (Box 65)
  - Internship Program. Informational pamphlet, UA015.011.065.00018 (Box 65)
  - Journalism Exchange Program (ASNE). Informational pamphlet-86, 1985 -- 1986; UA015.011.065.00019 (Box 65)
  - Power Projection and the Long-Range Combat Aircraft: Missions, Capabilities, and Alternative Designs. Special Report, 1981; UA015.011.065.00020 (Box 65)
  - Program in Southwest Asia and Islamic Civilization. Seminar series, 1987; UA015.011.065.00021 (Box 65)
  - Recruitment Guide and Employment Report, 1994; UA015.011.065.00022 (Box 65)
  - Fletcher Report, 1994; UA015.011.065.00023 (Box 65)
  - Fletcher Report, 1995; UA015.011.065.00024 (Box 65)
  - Report to the Dean-88, 1987 -- 1988; UA015.011.066.00001 (Box 66)
  - Report of the Dean-87, 1986 -- 1987; UA015.011.066.00002 (Box 66)
  - Report of the Dean-90, 1988 -- 1990; UA015.011.066.00003 (Box 66)
  - Resume books of the Fletcher School-86, 1985 -- 1986; UA015.011.066.00004 (Box 66)
  - Resume Books of the Fletcher School-91, 1990 -- 1991; UA015.011.066.00005 (Box 66)
  - SALT II and American Security. Special Report, 1980; UA015.011.066.00006 (Box 66)
  - Some Current Problems in Foreign Affairs, by Edmund A. Gullion, 1966; UA015.011.066.00007 (Box 66)
  - The Soviet Union and Ballistic Missile Defense. Special Report, 1980; UA015.011.066.00008 (Box 66)
  - A Testament of Faith. Commencement Address by Ruhl Jacob Bartlett, 1972; UA015.011.066.00009 (Box 66)
  - Thailand: National Development and International Role. Conference Report, 1982; UA015.011.066.00010 (Box 66)
  - University Consortium for Research on North America. Status Report, 1985; UA015.011.066.00011 (Box 66)
  - The Unnoticed Challenge, Soviet Maritime Strategy and the Global Choke Points. Special Report, 1980; UA015.011.066.00012 (Box 66)
  - The U.S. Defense Mobilization Infrastructure: Problems and Priorities. Conference Report, 1981; UA015.011.066.00013 (Box 66)
  - U.S. Strategic- Nuclear Policy and Ballistic Missile Defense: The 1980's and Beyond. Special Report, UA015.011.066.00014 (Box 66)
  - A World Legal Order: Law and Laws in Relation to World Law. Address by Roscoe Pound, 1959; UA015.011.066.00015 (Box 66)
  - Report of the Dean-87, 1986 -- 1987; UA015.011.066.00016 (Box 66)
  - Fletcher Notes, Volume 1 Numbers 1- 9, 1983; UA015.011.067.00001 (Box 67)
  - Fletcher Notes, Volume 1 Numbers 11-14, 1983; UA015.011.067.00002 (Box 67)
  - Fletcher Notes, Volume 1 Numbers 16-30, 1984; UA015.011.067.00003 (Box 67)
  - Fletcher Notes, Volume 2 Numbers 1-8, 1984; UA015.011.067.00004 (Box 67)
  - Fletcher Notes, Volume 2 Numbers 10-13, 1984; UA015.011.067.00005 (Box 67)
  - Fletcher Notes, Volume 2 Numbers 15-31, 1984 -- 1985; UA015.011.067.00006 (Box 67)
  - Fletcher Notes, Volume 3 Numbers 1-5, 1985; UA015.011.067.00007 (Box 67)
  - Fletcher Notes, Volume 3 Numbers 7-8, 1985; UA015.011.067.00008 (Box 67)
  - Fletcher Notes, Volume 3 Numbers 10-13, 1985; UA015.011.067.00009 (Box 67)
  - Fletcher Notes, Volume 3 Numbers 15-17, 1985 -- 1986; UA015.011.067.00010 (Box 67)
  - Fletcher Notes, Volume 3 Numbers 28-29, 31-32, 1986; UA015.011.067.00011 (Box 67)
  - America's Army Into the Twenty-first Century, 1993; UA015.011.068.00001 (Box 68)
  - Annual Review of Population Law, 1976; UA015.011.068.00002 (Box 68)
    Constitutions, Legislations, Regulations, Legal Options and Judicial Decisions
  - Both Swords & Plowshares: Military Roles in the 1990s, 1992, UA015.011.068.00003 (Box 68)
    Institute for Foreign Policy Analysis, National Security Paper Number 10
  - The Fletcher Mentor Program Directory, 1993; UA015.011.068.00004 (Box 68)
    The Fletcher Club of New York
  - Forced Migration: Policy Issues in the Post-Cold War World, 1993; UA015.011.068.00005 (Box 68)
  - Human Rights and Population: From the Perspectives of Law, Policy and Organization, 1973; UA015.011.068.00006 (Box 68)
    Law and Population Book Series, No. 5, Proceedings of the Second Annual Meeting of the International Advisory Committe on Population and Law Convened at the International House of Japan, Tokyo October 30-31, 1972.
  - The Korean War: Questions of Leadership, 1994; UA015.011.068.00007 (Box 68)
    North Pacific Program, The Sanwa Lecture Series
  - Law and Population in the Philippines, 1974; UA015.011.068.00008 (Box 68)
    Law and Population Book Series No. 9
  - la Ley y la Poblacion en Colombia, 1975; UA015.011.068.00009 (Box 68)
    Serie de Libros Sobre, la Ley y la Poblacion No. 10, Monografias de la CCRP, Vol. 2, junio 1975
  - Long-Range Bombers & the Role of Airpower in the New Century, 1995; UA015.011.068.00010 (Box 68)
    Foreword by Frank Carlucci
  - Mockba, 1994; UA015.011.068.00011 (Box 68)
    The Fletcher Summer Seminar, July 1994, North Pacific Program
  - News Clips, 2002; UA015.011.068.00012 (Box 68)
    Office of Public Affairs, May-November 2002.
  - Proliferation, Theater Missile Defense, and U.S. Security, 1994; UA015.011.068.00013 (Box 68)
    Report of an IFPA Working Group, The Institute for Foreign Policy Analysis
  - Public Regulation of Site-Selection for Nuclear Power Plants: Present Procedures and Reform Proposals, 1976; UA015.011.068.00014 (Box 68)
    An Annotated Bibliography, Program in International Policy, Resources and the Human Environment
  - Report of the Dean, 1992 -- 1993; UA015.011.068.00015 (Box 68)
  - Retaining Alliance Relevancy: NATO and the Combined Joint Task Force Concept, 1994; UA015.011.068.00016 (Box 68)
    National Security Paper Number Fifteen, Institute for Foreign Policy Analysis
  - Security Strategy & Missile Defense, 1996; UA015.011.068.00017 (Box 68)
    Institute of Foreign Policy Analysis
  - Seeing the Elephant: Leading America's Army into the Twenty-First Century, 1996; UA015.011.068.00018 (Box 68)
    Institute for Foreign Policy Analysis, National Security Paper Number Eighteen.
  - Taiwan in a Transformed Global Setting, 1994; UA015.011.068.00019 (Box 68)
    April 28-29, 2004, Summary of a Transpacific Dialogue, Institue for Foreign Policy
  - Taiwan in a Transformed World, 1995; UA015.011.068.00020 (Box 68)
    Institute for Foreign Policy
  - Fletcher Magazine, Spring, 2016; UA015.011.084.00003; 1 Folder(s) (Box 84)
  - Fletcher News Clips, Fall 1999 (folder 1), UA015.011.068.00021 (Box 68)
  - Fletcher News Clips, Fall 1999 (folder 2), UA015.011.068.00022 (Box 68)
  - Fletcher News Clips, Spring 1999 (March-May) part 1, UA015.011.068.00023 (Box 68)
  - Fletcher News Clips, Spring 1999 (March-May) part 2, UA015.011.068.00024 (Box 68)
  - Fletcher News Clips, Winter 1999 (December-February), UA015.011.068.00025 (Box 68)
  - Fletcher News Clips, Fall, 1998; UA015.011.068.00026 (Box 68)
  - Fletcher News Clips, Summer, 1998; UA015.011.068.00027 (Box 68)
  - Fletcher News Clips, 1998; UA015.011.068.00028 (Box 68)
  - Fletcher News Clips, 1997; UA015.011.068.00029 (Box 68)
  - The Fletcher Alumni Review, Fall, 1957; UA015.011.068.00030 (Box 68)
  - The Fletcher School Leadership Program for Financial Inclusion, policy memoranda, 2011; UA015.011.084.00001; 1 Folder(s) (Box 84)
  - Fletcher Security Review, 2015 -- 2016; UA015.011.084.00002; 1 Folder(s) (Box 84)
    Volume, Number
    3, 1
  - Foreign Affairs in the Seventies, 1971; UA015.011.068.00031 (Box 68)
  - Fletcher Magazine, Winter, 2017; UA015.011.084.00004; 1 Folder(s) (Box 84)
  - Fletcher Magazine, Winter, 2018; UA015.011.084.00006; 1 Folder(s) (Box 84)
    40, 1
  - Fletcher Magazine, Spring, 2015; UA015.011.00001; 1 Digital Object(s)
  - Fletcher Magazine, Fall, 2015; UA015.011.00002; 1 Digital Object(s)
  - Fletcher Magazine, Fall, 2016; UA015.011.00003; 1 Digital Object(s)
  - Fletcher Magazine, Summer, 2017; UA015.011.00004; 1 Digital Object(s)
  - Fletcher Magazine, Summer, 2018; UA015.011.00005; 1 Digital Object(s)
  - Fletcher Magazine, Summer 2019; UA015.003031 (Box 84, Folder 8)
    40, 2
  - A World of Crisis and Shifting Geopolitics: Greece, the Eastern Mediterranean and Europe, A Conference Report, 2011; UA015.003030 (Box 84, Folder 7)
- Fletcher program theses, 1981 -- 2015; UA015.012; 286 Digital Object(s); 1 Volumes
  This series contains selected theses submitted in fulfillment of the requirements for the following Fletcher School masters programs: Masters of Arts in Law and Diplomacy, Masters of International Business, Masters of Law in International Law, and Masters of Arts.
  This series is arranged chronologically by year.
  - Nationalism - Internationalism in the Philosophical Thought from Machiavelli to Mao, 1981; UA015.012.093.00003; 1 Volumes (Box 109, 93, Folder 3)
    Accession UA-2019-030.